<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[42]]></id><name><![CDATA[leguide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[LeGuide.com]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Smart shopping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[LeGuide.com allows you to make your site and your products known to millions of shoppers wanting to buy products and thus gaining the loyalty of new customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/42-leguidecom.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/42.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[LeGuide.com allows you to make your site and your products known to millions of shoppers wanting to buy products and thus gaining the loyalty of new customers. It is&nbsp;a fantastic window for e-merchants!   The LeGuide.com Group is the number 1 independent French publisher of shopping guides, shopping-based search engines and price comparison on the internet. It already exists in 14 countries and 9 different languages. LeGuide.com has been a trusted partner of shoppers and merchants since 1998: the former, it helps to find the most interesting product offers online and the latter it helps in improving their visibility and developing their operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module gives you the opportunity to develop your business and highlight your site your best deals!  When you sell products online, it&rsquo;s essential that potential customers can find their way to your site. Whether they are trying to unearth a particular product or are simply trying to find the cheapest offer, buyers are using shopping guides more and more; having a listing on a price comparison website is therefore vital if you want to make yourself known to millions of buyers about to make a purchase and thus boost your sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.16]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595088-pprod/leguidecom.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595088-pbig/leguidecom.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[367]]></id><name><![CDATA[banipmod]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ban IP addresses]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Ban unwelcome visitors from your shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/367-ban-ip-addresses.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/367.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Ban unwelcome visitors from your shop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Protect your site from ill-intentioned visitors and unwanted bots]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/613667-pprod/ban-ip-addresses.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/613667-pbig/ban-ip-addresses.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5 - Create ​​bundles of products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandising]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Allow the purchase of combinations of products with or without a discount, in one click  Would you like to increase your average shopping cart and at the same time, allow your customers to save money if they purchase several products simultaneously? It is now possible thanks to&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;!  Without waiting any longer, you can create packs of products that can be purchased in one click, without worrying about stock or their combinations.  A precious additional sales tool  Accompany your customers in their buying process, by offering them&nbsp;packs of coherent products&nbsp;that you will have predefined, just as the salesman in a real shop would do. Such as for example: this fantastic camera, memory card and tripod. You know that this selection is appropriate and that it will appeal to your customers.  Or you could even use your best-sellers, by adding them to those that are less visible, to allow your customers to discover them.  Your packs will need to be made up of 2 products minimum, the number is unlimited. Push the quantity per product, choose the combinations of your choice, there are multiple options allowing you to multiply the possibilities.  Would you like to reserve the purchase of a product within a pack? That is also possible! You will therefore be able&nbsp;to offer a free product&nbsp;if it is purchased as part of a pack. The possibilities are infinite!  Integrated assistant  It isn&#39;t always obvious deciding which products should be offered within a pack. Here again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution to the problem. When creating your pack, our module will supply you with strategic information, like the number of products sold or their available stock. There is also an integrated&nbsp;dynamic price simulator&nbsp;for your pack, to help you see more clearly when creating your business transaction, without you harming your profit margin.  Remain the maestro of combinations  One of the products that you have added to your pack is available in several colors, but you don&#39;t want to offer them all in this set? Advanced Pack&nbsp;will allow you to do this.  You will also have the possibility of predefining a combination by default, for each of the products of your pack, even if it&#39;s different to the one defined in your catalog.  Your customers will then be able to&nbsp;personalise their selection&nbsp;amongst the characteristics that you will have chosen to integrate in the offer.  Business Incentive  Incentive is something that motivates your visitor to make a purchase The main aim is to convince more of your site visitors to finish their order and/or&nbsp;spend more money per transaction. Perhaps you have already tried, by offering free delivery over a certain amount of purchases, or to offer discounts on certain products or even to send discount vouchers? All of these methods work, but their range is limited, as these promotions are usually temporary due to their excessive cost! Stop looking, you have already found the solution !  To entice your customers,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will give you the choice of applying a discount when all the products in the shopping cart are ordered, thus encouraging the purchase of the whole pack.  3 possibilities are available:&nbsp;Offer a specific discount on&nbsp;each product&nbsp;in the packApply a general discount on&nbsp;the set of productsApply a&nbsp;fixed price, such as a psychological price, for example Advanced Pack&nbsp;will also be able to manage the discounts already applied to your products, allowing you to integrate them in the pack price, or on the contrary, to exclude them, in order to choose the predefined discount on the pack. This decision will be made even easier thanks to our&nbsp;clear and clean-looking interface, that will allow you to see the discounted products very easily.  You won&#39;t need to worry about the coherence of your prices anymore  Have you ever had to review all the prices in your catalog, to detect any possible incoherences and correct them? What would happen if you had to manually manage the repercussions of these changes in product pricing in your packs? This would represent a significant extra workload if if it&#39;s not anticipated within the choice of management solutions within your packs!  Once again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution.  By default, in the case where no reduction has been applied, the pack price is the sum of the products making it up. Should you need to modify the price of a product after having created the pack,&nbsp;the pack price will automatically be updated, and without you having to intervene.  In those cases where you will apply a discount to one or more products in an existing pack, and on condition you have authorized the&nbsp;promotional implications, the pack price will also be changed, showing your customers the discount that has been applied.  Is one of the products of your pack subject to an green-tax? No problem, it will automatically be reflected in the pack price and will be clearly stated, guaranteeing absolute&nbsp;respect for the legislation.  Regarding the management of your stock, everything has been automated!  For each pack ordered, the product stocks it contains will be&nbsp;automatically deducted. This way you will avoid the double management of stock or the frustration generated by sales rendered impossible, due to the bad assignation of quantities. Also, in the case where a product in a pack is out of stock, it will&nbsp;automatically be displayed as unavailable&nbsp;for purchase thanks to an availability warning system that is both elegant and modern.  For your customers, we have integrated a graphic and fun notification system, allowing the instant identification of stock shortages on combinations or products making up the pack.&nbsp;There&#39;s no chance of you receiving orders for products that are out of stock !  Highlight your packs and sell more  Once you have defined your pack, you will be able to configure it in the same way as you would a classic product. Everything is possible, such as assigning it customized images, classing it in the category of your choice,&nbsp;optimizing your SEO, writing a customized description, attributing it an EAN code or a specific reference, configuring its volume to calculate delivery costs, etc...  For those that are pressed for time, and in order to facilitate their marketing,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will automatically display all the photos of the products that make it up, as well as their descriptions, in the form of tabs. Your customers will be correctly informed, without leaving the page of your pack, and&nbsp;able to finalise their purchase in one click.  And that&#39;s not all... For more visibility, your packs will automatically be&nbsp;highlighted on their data sheets&nbsp;for those being sold in lots This way, you will encourage your customers to order the pack, rather than the product they were initially interested in. Essentially, this is&nbsp;cross-selling: an accessible method of&nbsp;increasing your average shopping cart&nbsp;!  We don&#39;t forget designers  From the beginning, we have integrated the fact that this module should be easily adapted by your web agency or designer/integrator. The module adapts itself perfectly to the default PrestaShop 1.5 and 1.6 themes, whilst allowing the most advanced graphic personalization.  A set of JavaScript templates and CSS style sheets are delivered as models with the module,&nbsp;to facilitate the integration process. Either yourself or your integrator will therefore be able to use all of the functionalities of the&nbsp;Advanced Pack 5&nbsp;engine, in order to present them in the graphic form that will best correspond with the general atmosphere of your online store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[269.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping & Delivery]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Offer your customers delivery via UPS, the essential e-commerce shipper, and view tracking information for your shipments directly from your PrestaShop back office]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-logistics-delivery-prestashop-modules/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Offer your customers delivery via UPS, the essential e-commerce shipper, and view tracking information for your shipments directly from your PrestaShop back office.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve trust in your site by offering shipments via UPS, the leading package delivery service in the United States.Optimize your conversions by offering quick and trackable delivery to your customers.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1615]]></id><name><![CDATA[gshopping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Shopping]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Smart shopping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Massively boost traffic and sales by presenting your products on Google Shopping, and promote your store among millions of online shoppers using Google! &nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/comparison-shopping-prestashop/1615-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1615.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Massively boost traffic and sales by presenting your products on Google Shopping, and promote your store among millions of online shoppers using Google! &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your trafficGive visibility to your entire catalog directly on Google Shopping, by presenting images of your products. &nbsp;Save timeIt&#39;s easy to export your entire product catalog and sync it in one click with Google Shopping &nbsp;Increase your conversion rateVisitors coming from Google Shopping have selected your product from the competing images shown, which means they are ready to finalize their order on your site.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595182-pprod/google-shopping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595182-pbig/google-shopping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world&rsquo;s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons&nbsp; since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.022]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Search & Filter]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner - Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/search-filters-prestashop-modules/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner - Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Provide to your customers the products that meet their needs.  Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products, Advanced Search 4 can add as many search engines as you want and place them in different places on your website. This module was developed in an effort to provide short loading times, even on large catalogs. Your visitors can browse products that match their search criteria, to make their purchases in minimal time.  Winner of the Best PrestaShop Modules Awards 2012  Advanced Search 4 won the Best module of the year Award at the PrestaShop BarCamp of Barcelona (Spain)!  Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products.  Advanced Search 4 adds the multi-layered navigation, search by step, filters and multi-criteria searches. Each search is saved over the navigation, allowing your visitors to return to the results of their research at any time.  Google is his friend  This PrestaShop Addon is a small revolution for SEO. Advanced Search 4 generate a mass-produced products pages optimized for SEO, and without duplicate content! Pick up your criteria on which you want to improve your SEO, validate them, and here you go with hundreds of pages listing your products, including: re-written URL, H1 tags, description, meta tags, automatised cross links...   To maximize your reputation, these results pages can be shared on most social networks places around the internet, as well as sent by e-mail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.10.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Quick / Mass Edit]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products!You have over than 100 products?  You want to control the association of your products to your categories?  This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/bulk-update-prestashop-modules/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products!You have over than 100 products?  You want to control the association of your products to your categories?  This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time!In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category.Look for products that you want to add this category and add 1 click!You also control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/51759-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/51759-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanagerforprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily]]></description><author><![CDATA[eMagicOne]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily tasks&nbsp;and making it simple to update your shop. &nbsp; Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management. Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE *** &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; Spend an Hour, Save a Day! Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds. For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you. &nbsp; Take Your Online Business to the Bank Buy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules. Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689783-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689783-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3162]]></id><name><![CDATA[webcallback]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Call Back]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!  Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3162-web-call-back.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3162.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Add the Call Back module to your online store to increase sales!  Nothing is more frustrating than getting through to a company, just to be put on hold. Stop wasting customers&rsquo; time with the Call Back Module. Let customers leave their contact information for you to contact them at a convenient time. Capture customers you would have otherwise lost.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611422-pprod/web-call-back.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611422-pbig/web-call-back.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save valuable time by automating the preparation of your delivery labels! Prepare and print your delivery labels, and stick them right on the packages for the orders you&#39;re shipping]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save valuable time by automating the preparation of your delivery labels! Prepare and print your delivery labels, and stick them right on the packages for the orders you&#39;re shipping.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time shipping your ordersLower your rate of returned packages due to wrong addresses]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3438]]></id><name><![CDATA[auctions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Auctions]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Front office features]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/front-office-features-prestashop-modules/3438-auctions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3438.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. With a number of great features and intuitive interface, this is the best auctions module available for Prestashop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. Auctions are the great way to attract and keep customers in your shop. You will be sure that customer is paying right price for your products. You don't have to negotiate prices with customers anymore. Managing auctions is very intuitive, and fully integrated with your shop. You will feel like it's not a module but integral part of the PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625145-pprod/auctions.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625145-pbig/auctions.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3511]]></id><name><![CDATA[priceminister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PriceMinister]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace & Affiliation Platforms]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-prestashop-modules/3511-priceminister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3511.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of the PriceMinister audience with its 2 million visitors a year and its 20 million subscribed members and boost your sales with your super PriceMinister store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the PriceMinister for Prestashop module, your processing is automated, the products are exported directly to the PriceMinister marketplace and your orders are automatically imported and integrated into your Prestashop store.   You also automate communication with your customers: your order confirmations are sent directly to the customer by email via the PriceMinister web service, customers are automatically notified and the status of your orders is automatically updated.  By using the PriceMinister module, you maintain control of your offer and product flows, you automatically import your orders without additional cost or subscription and your data exchanges are automated and free.  Integration is easy and convenient: you configure your module, your export becomes automatic and so you have no more data to manipulate  Implementing scheduled tasks is simple and automated thanks to compatibility with the Prestashop Cron task-scheduling editor module (free). Just click on a button to automatically integrate your scheduled tasks in the module. It is still possible to manually configure your tasks.  The module design is based on the online merchant experience. The module was conceived by an online merchant in the service of his colleagues and developed by professional developers, which gives it ease of use and maximum effectiveness.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support which is assured unconditionally up to the moment of making the products available online and the import of your first orders.  You must have a PriceMinister PRO account.  New version, PriceMinister v4: export XML, simplified configuration, native scheduled tasks, intelligent mapping, sleek design and improved ergonomics.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.09]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[244.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[144.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/654537-pprod/priceminister.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/654537-pbig/priceminister.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation FB]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !  This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Loyalty"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-2015-loyalty.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4549]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmurealtimestats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Real Time Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Stats]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop !With this module you are no longer blind! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/4549-dmu-real-time-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4549.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop !With this module you are no longer blind! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module lets you know exactly what is happening on your shop.Now you are able to visualize the path of a visitor, his reactions on each page visited, ease or blocking steps in the ordering process ... ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/324796-pprod/dmu-real-time-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/324796-pbig/dmu-real-time-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4932]]></id><name><![CDATA[mynewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter & Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Advertising & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- a]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/advertising-marketing-newsletter-modules/4932-newsletter-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4932.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The best way to convert, build loyalty and keep in touch with customers is with our Newsletter with Statistics Module! This brilliant module helps you send gorgeous newsletters to customer groups -- and help keep them coming back to shop!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Track the effectiveness of each newsletter. Every KPI you, as an online merchant, should monitor is available at your fingertips. These key statistics allow online merchants to monitor newsletters to see which work and which don&rsquo;t to improve newsletter mailings.  Additional benefits include:Inform customers about sales, company or industry news, new products, etc.Personalize newsletters (to echo your brand identity)Build customer loyalty to your brandStay in touch with your customers]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.24]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595046-pprod/newsletter-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595046-pbig/newsletter-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a better place on Google.  To optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an internal linking that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.1.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Stats]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-stats-prestashop-modules/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop&#39;s and products&#39; profitability !  The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly,&nbsp;profit and profit margin.  Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like &quot;what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?&quot;.  This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV&nbsp;file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.    You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.2.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Time Saver"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-2015-savetime.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/543344-pprod/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/543344-pbig/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5275]]></id><name><![CDATA[productsbycategoryslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider - Products of same category]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Slideshows]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/slideshows-prestashop-modules/5275-slider-products-of-same-category.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5275.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Submit items of the same class on your product pages with this slider at the bottom of the page, and improve the navigation of your customers, along with your average basket!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to make cross-selling of other products in each category, and increase your average shopping basket.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/625266-pprod/slider-products-of-same-category.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625266-pbig/slider-products-of-same-category.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5542]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderpreparation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy order preparation]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administrative tools]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[ Save precious minutes every day by optimizing your logistics]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/administration-tools-prestashop-modules/5542-easy-order-preparation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5542.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[ Save precious minutes every day by optimizing your logistics.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save timeSimplify your logistics]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.6]]></version